Dave Chapman Papers
Dave Chapman Papers
1932-1972
Chapman, Dave, 1909-1978.
57.0 linear ft.
Papers of the American industrial designer. Collection includes correspondence (1940-1965), blueprints, design drawings, notes, photographs, renderings, reports, pamphlets, clippings (1932-1965) and color slides, 1966.
148895
Biographical History
Dave Chapman was born Jan. 30, 1909, in Gilman, Illinois. He graduated from the Armour Institute of Technology in 1932. That same year he worked on the design and planning of the Chicago Century of Progress. After this, he was employed in the product design division of Montgomery Ward and Company. From 1935 to 1955, he was senior partner in the industrial design firm of Dave Chapman Industrial Design. Since 1955 he has served as president of Design Research, Inc. as well as head of his own firm. Chapmen is past president of the Society of Industrial Designers and is a recipient of the Design Award Medal given by the Industrial Designers Institute. He is a fellow of the International Institute of Arts and Letters and lives with his wife and two daughters in Chicago, Illinois.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Dave Chapman Papers includes correspondence, published material, photographs, designs, renderings, and related items. The collection consists of two large accessions which have not been integrated, and several smaller additions.
1968 accession
The first of the two large accessions, the 1968 accession is divided into three series. Correspondence (1968 accession) is divided into General Correspondence Files and Chronological Log-Outgoing Correspondence. General Correspondence Files consists of incoming correspondence and is arranged chronologically, then alphabetically by subject. Chronological Log-Outgoing Correspondence consists of replies to incoming mail and is arranged chronologically.
Subject files (1968 accession) includes correspondence, blueprints, designs, plans, notes, drawings, clippings, photographs, reports, color charts, printed matter, published material, and related items. The material is filed alphabetically by subject.
Color Slides (1968 accession) consists of one box of color slides.
General files
General files, the second of the two large accessions, includes printed material correspondence, photographs, presentations, proposals, and other material. There are also a large number of slides. Companies represented include Allied Farm Equipment, Corning Glass, Elizabeth Arden, Ford, International Harvester, Maytag, Memorex, Montgomery Ward, RCA, Sears, the United States Air Force Academy, Westclox, and many others. Also in this series is work done for the International Cooperation Adminstration, for Costa Rica, Surinam, El Salvador, and Iran. This accession has not been processed and remains in original order; the related portion of the inventory below is a box listing only.
Other additions
Advertising work contains material added to the collection in 1969. Firms represented include Hamilton Beach, Interstate United, Laurentide Biere-Ale, Maytag and Co., Owens-Corning, and Simoniz. The advertising work consists of artists' ideas and models, sketches, negative copies of completed work, and proposals for advertising campaigns. About half of the material relates to Simoniz products and packaging lines. Packages 5 and 9 also contain related correspondence.
Design projects consists mainly of sketches and presentation panels but also includes photographs, proofs, pamphlets, brochures and other material for a variety of clients including Allied Farm Equipment, Cooper's, Corning Glass, Hankscraft, Hamilton Beach, Johnson Motors, Libby's, Owens-Corning, Panelfab, Simoniz, Speed-o-print, Wheland, and others. The cardboard cases in Package 5 contains samples of both packaging and actual shorts, socks, t-shirts, etc. for the Jockey label of Cooper's Inc.
Renderings consists of drawings for a variety of clients including Baxter Laboratories, Beltone Hearing Aid, Corning Glass, Hamilton Beach, Imperial Tobacco Company, Molson Breweries, Montgomery Ward, Parker Pen, Rutger's University, and others.
Arrangement of the Collection
See Scope and Contents above. Note that box and package numbers are not unique; when requesting material, please specify series title and box/package number to ensure retrieval of correct items.
Related Material
has the papers of a number of noted industrial designers. Please refer to the for a complete listing. See also the
Industrial Design Society Records
.
Subject and Genre Headings
Industrial Design; Chapman, Dave, 1909-1978 Archives.; Design, Industrial, United States.; Industrial designers, United States.; Art and industry.; Blueprints (reprographic copies); Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Design drawings.; Drawings (visual works); Pamphlets.; Photographs.; Slides (photographs); Industrial designers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- Correspondence (1968 accession)
  - General correspondence
    - 1940-1944 (Box I / 1)
    - 1947 (Box I / 1)
    - 1948 (Box I / 1)
    - 1949 (Box I / 1)
    - 1955-1956
      - ASID-Board of Directors Correspondence (Box I / 1)
    - 1956
      - ASID-General Correspondence (Box I / 1)
      - ASID-Committee Reports (Box I / 1)
      - Bills - Dave Chapman, General Correspondence (Box I / 1)
    - 1956-1957
      - ASID-Board of Directors (Box I / 1)
    - 1957
      - Bills - Dave Chapman, General Correspondence (Box I / 1)
      - Bills - Eileen Chapman, General Correspondence (Box I / 1)
      - Boat: Correspondence (Box I / 2)
      - Boat: Correspondence, Equipment Catalogues (Box I / 2)
      - Boat: Correspondence, Listings (Box I / 2)
      - Family Correspondence (Box I / 2)
      - Staff Meetings Correspondence (Box I / 2)
      - Travel: Correspondence (Box I / 2)
    - 1957-1958
      - ASID-Annual Meeting: Bedford Springs (Box I / 2)
      - ASID-Board of Directors: Correspondence (Box I / 2)
    - 1958
      - Bills - Dave Chapman, General Correspondence (Box I / 2)
      - Bills - Eileen Chapman, General Correspondence (Box I / 2)
      - Boat: Correspondence (Box I / 2)
      - Boat: Correspondence, Equipment Catalogues (Box I / 3)
      - Boat: Correspondence, Listings (Box I / 3)
      - Farnily Correspondence (Box I / 3)
      - Ford Foundation - Visual Arts (Box I / 3)
      - Travel: Correspondence (Box I / 3)
      - Doodles (Box I / 3)
      - Miscellaneous: Mailings, Clips, etc. (Box I / 3)
    - 1958-1959
      - ASID-Board of Directors (Box I / 3)
      - ASID-Committee: Design Protection (Box I / 3)
      - ASID-Committee: Ford Foundation (Box I / 4)
      - ASID-Committee: Governrnent Regulations (Box I / 4)
      - ASID-Committee: School Approval Program, 4 folders (Box I / 4)
      - ASID-Committee: School Approval Program, 3 folders (Box I / 5)
    - 1959
      - Bills - Dave Chapnan, General Correspondence (Box I / 5)
      - Bills - Eileen Chapman, General Correspondence (Box I / 5)
      - Boat Correspondence - Equipment; Catalogues I (Box I / 5)
      - Boat Correspondence - Equipment Catalogues II (Box I / 6)
      - Travel Correspondence (Box I / 6)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box I / 6)
    - 1960
      - Aluminum Company of America - Correspondence (Box I / 6)
      - American Bakeries Company - Correspondence (Box I / 6)
      - American Management Association - Correspondence (Box I / 6)
      - ASID-General Correspondence (Box I / 6)
      - ASID-Newsletter (Box I / 6)
      - Baxter Laboratories, Inc. (Box I / 7)
      - Beltone Hearing Aid Company (Box I / 7)
      - Bendix Products Division (Box I / 7)
      - Black, Sivalls & Bryson, Inc. (Box I / 7)
      - Boat: Correspondence (Box I / 7)
      - Boat: Correspondence, Catalogues (Box I / 7)
      - Boat: Correspondence, Listings (Box I / 8)
      - Bramer Manufacturing Company (Box I / 8)
      - Brunswick-Balke-Collender Comapny (Box I / 8)
      - Brunswick School Equipment (Box I / 8)
      - Brunswick Sports Products Company (Box I / 8)
      - Bryant Manufacturing Company (Box I / 8)
      - Budding, Carl & Company (Box I / 8)
      - Burgess Vibrocrafters, Inc. (Box I / 8)
      - Check-out Sheets (Box I / 8)
      - City National Bank and Trust Company (Box I / 8)
      - Continental Assurance Company (Box I / 8)
      - Continental Casualty Company (Box I / 8)
      - Continental National Group (Box I / 8)
      - Cooper's, Inc. (Box I / 8)
      - Corning Glass Works (Box I / 8)
      - Doodles (Box I / 9)
      - Educational Facilities Laboratories (Box I / 9)
      - Eljer Company (Box I / 9)
      - Employees, Correspondence re (Box I / 9)
      - Esquire Radio Corporation (Box I / 9)
      - Family Correspondence (Box I / 9)
      - Felt Products Manufacturing Company (Box I / 9)
      - Food Packaging Council (Box I / 9)
      - Gift Ideas (Box I / 9)
      - Gilson Brothers (Box I / 9)
      - Hamilton Beach Company (Box I / 9)
      - Hankscraft Company (Box I / 9)
      - Hotel Reservations (Box I / 9)
      - Hussmann Refrigerator Company (Box I / 10)
      - Illinois Chamber of Commerce (Box I / 10)
      - Illinois Testing Laboratories (Box I / 10)
      - Information, Request for (Box I / 10)
      - Inter-Office Memoranda (Box I / 10)
      - ICA - General Correspondence (Box I / 10)
      - ICA - Teheran/Beirut (Box I / 10)
      - ICA - General Correspondence: Samples, Lists, Expenses (Box I / 10)
      - ICA - General Correspondence: Miscellaneous Data (Box I / 10)
      - International Harvester Company (Box I / 11)
      - Johnson Motors (Box I / 11)
      - [Eli] Lilly and Company (Box I / 11)
      - Master Electric Division (Box I / 11)
      - Molson's Brewery, Ltd. (Box I / 11)
      - Montgomery Ward and Company, 2 folders (Box I / 11)
      - Moto-Mower Division (Box I / 11)
      - My Maid Corporation (Box I / 11)
      - Nimrod Manufacturing Company (Box I / 11)
      - Office, Supply Sources (Box I / 11)
      - Oriental Institute (the) (Box I / 11)
      - Outboard Marine Corporation (Box I / 11)
      - Package Designers Council (Box I / 11)
      - Portable Elevator Manufacturing Company (Box I / 11)
      - Reeves Pully Company (Box I / 11)
      - Rutgers University (Box I / 11)
      - School Brochures (Box I / 11)
      - Scovill Manufacturing Company (Box I / 11)
      - Siegler Corporation (Box I / 11)
      - Simoniz Company (Box I / 12)
      - Society of Typographic Arts (Box I / 12)
      - Speed-O-Print Corporation (Box I / 12)
      - Stephens College (Box I / 12)
      - Stewart Warner Corporation (Box I / 12)
      - Subscriptions, Correspondence re (Box I / 12)
      - United Carriers and Fabricators, Inc. (Box I / 12)
      - U.S. Cap and Closure, Inc. (Box I / 12)
      - Westmore Products (Box I / 12)
      - Wheland Company (the) (Box I / 12)
      - White Sewing Machine Corporation (Box I / 12)
      - Worthington Corporation (Buffalo) (Box I / 12)
      - Worthington Corporation (Harrison) (Box I / 12)
      - Worthington Corporation (Holyoke) (Box I / 12)
      - Yamasaki, Kim (Box I / 12)
      - Zeo-Ran Company (the) (Box I / 12)
      - Miscellaneous Letters, 2 folders (Box I / 12)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box I / 12)
    - 1960-1961
      - ASID-Board of Directors: Correspondence (Box I / 13)
      - ASID-Board of Directors: Meeting Minutes (Box I / 13)
      - ASID-Committee: Patent (Box I / 13)
      - ASID-Committee: Triennale (Box I / 13)
      - Annual Reports (Box I / 13)
    - 1961
      - ASID - Correspondence (Box I / 13)
      - ASID - Correspondence, General (Box I / 13)
      - ASID-Newsletter Bookkeeping, Correspondence re (Box I / 13)
      - Check-out Sheets (Box I / 14)
      - Employees, Correspondence re (Box I / 14)
      - Gift Ideas Goldsmith, William M., F ASID (Box I / 14)
      - Information, Requests for (Box I / 14)
      - Inter-Office Memoranda (Box I / 14)
      - Office, Supply Sources (Box I / 14)
      - Public Relations, 2 folders (Box I / 14)
      - Sales Reports (Box I / 14)
      - School Brochures (Box I / 14)
      - Small Business Administration (Box I / 14)
      - Subscriptions, Correspondence re (Box I / 15)
      - Yamasaki, Kim (Box I / 15)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box I / 15)
    - 1962
      - Family Correspondence (Box I / 15)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 2 folders (Box I / 15)
    - 1963
      - Family Correspondence (Box I / 15)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 2 folders (Box I / 15)
    - 1964
      - General Correspondence (Box I / 15)
    - 1965
      - General Correspondence (Box I / 15)
  - Chronological log - Outgoing correspondence
    - 1958-1959
      - Dave Chapman General (Box I / 16)
      - Public Relations (Box I / 16)
      - Yamasaki, Kim (Box I / 16)
    - 1960
      - ASID General (Box I / 16)
      - Dave Chapman (Box I / 17)
      - Employee Relations (Box I / 17)
      - Goldsmith, William M. (Box I / 17)
      - Public Relations (Box I / 17)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box I / 17)
      - Jan-Jun, 3 folders (Box I / 18)
      - Jul-Dec, 3 folders (Box I / 19)
    - 1961
      - Jan-Jun, 3 folders (Box I / 20)
      - Jul-Dec, 3 folders (Box I / 21)
- Subject files (1968 accession)
  - Brunswick Corporation, 1956-1965 (Box II / 1)
  - Burgess Vibrocrafters, Inc., 1953-1960 (Box II / 1)
  - CGY, Inc., 1958-1960 (Box II / 1)
  - CGY, Inc. - Sop Material, 1958-1966 (Box II / 1)
  - Chicago Sun Times, 1954-1963 (Box II / 2)
  - Collected Views: Value of Industrial Designer to Industry, 1955-1960 (Box II / 2)
  - Craft Horizons, 1953-1963 (Box II / 2)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box II / 3)
    - Acoustical Drape, Inquiries re, 1960-1962 (Box II / 3)
    - Acoustical Material, 1961 (Box II / 3)
    - Acoustical Notes, 1959-1963 (Box II / 3)
    - Acoustical Notes, 1959 (Box II / 3)
    - Acoustical Notes, Celotex Corporation, 1950 (Box II / 3)
    - Adler Electronics, Inc., 1958-1959 (Box II / 3)
    - Air Conditioning-Heating, 1959-1960 (Box II / 3)
    - Ampex Corporation, 1959-1961 (Box II / 4)
    - Architectural Forum, 1957-1959 (Box II / 4)
    - Audio-Visual Equipment and Services, 1959-1961 (Box II / 4)
    - Blinds, 1957-1959 (Box II / 5)
    - Boston University, 1957 (Box II / 5)
    - Blueprints and Plans, undated (Box II / 5)
    - Brunswick-Balke-Collender, 1958-1960 (Box II / 5)
    - Building Material: Johns-Manville Sales Corporation, 1961 (Box II / 6)
    - Building Material: Northrop Corporation, undated (Box II / 6)
    - Building Material: United States Plywood Corporation, undated (Box II / 6)
    - Building Material: Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box II / 6)
    - Carpeting, 1961 (Box II / 6)
    - Cerritos Junior College (floor plan), undated (Box II / 6)
    - Chalkboards and Accessories, 1963 (Box II / 6)
    - Chapman Report, 1960; 2 folders (Box II / 6)
    - Chapman Report, 1960 (Box II / 7)
    - Chicago City Junior College, 1958-1959 (Box II / 7)
    - Chicago Public Schools, 1959-1962 (Box II / 7)
    - Chicago Schools Journal, 1958-1959 (Box II / 7)
    - Chicago Teachers College (plan), undated (Box II / 7)
    - Classroom Designs, 1961 (Box II / 8)
    - Classroom Equipment and Supplies, 1959-1960 (Box II / 8)
    - Classroom Floor Coverings, 1959-1960 (Box II / 8)
    - Classroom Modernization, 1958-1959 (Box II / 8)
    - Classroom Television Receivers, 1958-1960 (Box II / 8)
    - Cleveland Board of Education (floor plans), undated (Box II / 9)
    - Cleveland School System, 1958-1959 (Box II / 9)
    - Color Charts and Floor Plan, undated (Box II / 9)
    - Copy from Jonathan King, 1960 (Box II / 9)
    - Corning Glass Works, 1960 (Box II / 9)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box II / 9)
    - Conant Report (the), 1959 (Box II / 10)
    - Current Population Report, 1960 (Box II / 10)
    - Current Population Report, 1962 (Box II / 10)
    - Current Population Report, 1963 (Box II / 10)
    - Dage-Educational TV System, 1960 (Box II / 10)
    - Decorating Schools, 1959 (Box II / 10)
    - Doors, 1959 (Box II / 10)
    - Drawings - Track and Hardware, 1960 (Box II / 10)
    - Drinking Fountains - Hawks Drinking Faucet Company, 1961 (Box II / 10)
    - Drinking Fountains - Kohler Company, 1962 (Box II / 10)
    - Eastman Kodak Company, 1959-1960 (Box II / 11)
    - Educational Screen and Audiovisual, 1959-1960 (Box II / 11)
    - Electron Corporation, 1962 (Box II / 11)
    - Electronic Futures, Inc., 1962 (Box II / 11)
    - Entron, Inc., 1960 (Box II / 11)
    - Final Report - EFL 304, 1960 (Box II / 11)
    - Floor Plans (oversize), undated (Box II / 38)
    - Florida State Dept. of Education, 1958-1959 (Box II / 12)
    - Fortune Directory, 1962 (Box II / 12)
    - Fund for the Advancement of Education (the), 1959 (Box II / 12)
    - Furniture, 1959-1960 (Box II / 12)
    - General Electric Co.npany, 1960-1962 (Box II / 12)
    - General Precision Laboratory, Inc., 1961 (Box II / 12)
    - Hagerstown, Maryland, 1958-1959 (Box II / 13)
    - Hardware: Russwin Division of the American Hardware Corp., undated (Box II / 13)
    - Hillsdale High School, 1959 (Box II / 13)
    - Hilltop School (blueprint), undated (Box II / 13)
    - Illinios State Chamber of Commerce - Education Dept., 1959 (Box II / 13)
    - Industrial Arts Equipment, 1961 (Box II / 13)
    - Jefferson County, Kentucky, 1958 (Box II / 13)
    - Jerrold Electronics Corporation, 1959 (Box II / 13)
    - Joint Council on Educational Television, 1958-1959 (Box II / 13)
    - Journal of Educational Sociology, 1959 (Box II / 13)
    - Language Labs
      - Dictaphone Corporation, 1961 (Box II / 14)
      - EDU-Tronics, Inc. (Box II / 14)
      - Electronic Futures, Inc. (Box II / 14)
      - Radio Corporation of America (Box II / 14)
      - Rheem Califone Corporation (Box II / 14)
      - Ewitchcraft, Inc. (Box II / 14)
      - Thompson-Ramo-Woolridge (Box II / 14)
      - Viewlex, Inc. (Box II / 14)
      - Webster Electric Company (Box II / 14)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box II / 14)
    - Large Screen Projection, 1960 (Box II / 14)
    - Lead Curtain, 1959 (Box II / 14)
    - Lead Curtain Wall, 1960-1961 (Box II / 15)
    - Libbey-Owens-Ford Glass Company, 1959 (Box II / 15)
    - Library Furniture (Box II / 15)
    - Library Furniture, 1963 (Box II / 15)
    - Library Plans, 1961; 2 folders (Box II / 15)
    - Library Study, 1960-1961 (Box II / 15)
    - Library Study, 1961 (Box II / 15)
    - Library and Independent Study, 1961 (Box II / 15)
    - Lighting, 1959-1960 (Box II / 16)
    - Magnetic Recording Industries, 1959 (Box II / 16)
    - Meeting Reports, 1959 (Box II / 16)
    - Midwest Program on Airborne Television Instruction, 1961-1962 (Box II / 17)
    - Milwaukee Public Schools, 1959 (Box II / 17)
    - Monsanto Chemical Company, 1959 (Box II / 17)
    - Movable Partitions, 1962; 4 folders (Box II / 17)
    - Movable Partitions, 1962 (Box II / 18)
    - Movie Projectors, 1961 (Box II / 18)
    - National Academy of Science, 1959 (Box II / 18)
    - National Association of Educational Broadcasters, 1959 (Box II / 18)
    - National Education Association Reports, 1960 (Box II / 18)
    - Opaque Projection, 1960 (Box II / 18)
    - Overhead Projector, 1961 (Box II / 18)
    - Overhead Projection, 1959 (Box II / 18)
    - Patents, 1932-1960 (Box II / 18)
    - Penn. State University, 1958-1959 (Box II / 18)
    - Penn. State University - Statistical Material, 1959-1960 (Box II / 18)
    - Philco Corporation, 1960 (Box II / 19)
    - Phono Players, 1961-1962 (Box II / 19)
    - Photographs - oversize (Box II / 38)
    - Pittsburgh School System Reports, 1959 (Box II / 19)
    - Plumbing Fixtures - Kohler Company (Box II / 19)
    - Portland Cement Association (Box II / 19)
    - Profiles of Significant Schools, 1962 (Box II / 19)
    - Projection - Light Levels, 1959 (Box II / 19)
    - Radio Corporation of America, 1956-1961 (Box II / 19)
    - Radios - Rheem Califone Corporation (Box II / 19)
    - Rear Screen Projection Equipment, 1959 (Box II / 20)
    - Rear Screen Projection Equipment, 1962 (Box II / 20)
    - Requests for Design Assistance, 1959-1960 (Box II / 20)
    - Research Reports, 1960-1961 (Box II / 20)
    - Research Material, 1960; 2 folders (Box II / 20)
    - Research Material, 1959-1961 (Box II / 21)
    - Research Material - Lead Curtain Wall, 1959-1961 (Box II / 21)
    - San Francisco State College, 1959 (Box II / 21)
    - Setchell-Carlson, Inc., 1960 (Box II / 21)
    - School Air Conditioning, 1959 (Box II / 22)
    - School Air Conditioning, 1961 (Box II / 22)
    - School Air Conditioning, 1962 (Box II / 22)
    - School Air Conditioning (Box II / 22)
    - School Executive (the), 1959 (Box II / 22)
    - School Furniture, 1961 (Box II / 22)
    - School Furniture (Box II / 22)
    - School Heating, 1961; 3 folders (Box II / 22)
    - School Heating (Box II / 22)
    - School Lighting, 1962 (Box II / 22)
    - School Management, 1961 (Box II / 22)
    - School Plans, 1962-1963 (Box II / 22)
    - Sony Corporation, 1960 (Box II / 22)
    - Space Communications, Inc., 1961 (Box II / 22)
    - Space Dividers, Movable, 1959-1960 (Box II / 22)
    - Special Reports, 1962 (Box II / 22)
    - Special Reports, 1961 (Box II / 22)
    - Special Statistical Reports, 1960-1961 (Box II / 23)
    - Statistical Census and Figures, 1950-1959 (Box II / 23)
    - Statistical Material, 1959 (Box II / 23)
    - Statistical Material, 1960-1962 (Box II / 23)
    - Statistical Material, 1900-1965 (Box II / 23)
    - Statistical Reports - Duplicates, 1953-1965 (Box II / 23)
    - Still Projectors, 1961 (Box II / 24)
    - Stoddard Plan (the), 1958-1959 (Box II / 24)
    - Structural Materials, 1959-1961 (Box II / 24)
    - Tape Accessories, 1961 (Box II / 24)
    - Tape Accessories, 1960 (Box II / 24)
    - Tape Recorders, 1961-1962 (Box II / 24)
    - Tape Recorders, 1959 (Box II / 24)
    - Tape Recorders, 1962; 2 folders (Box II / 24)
    - Tape Recorders, 1960 (Box II / 24)
    - Tape Recorders, 1961 (Box II / 24)
    - Tapes - Minnesota Mining & Manufacturing Company, 1961 (Box II / 24)
    - Tapes - Rheem Califone Corporation, 1960-1961 (Box II / 24)
    - Teaching Machines
      - 1961 (Box II / 24)
      - 1961, 2 folders (Box II / 25)
      - 1962, 2 folders (Box II / 25)
      - 1961, 2 folders (Box II / 25)
      - Electronic Futures, Inc., 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - General Atronics Corporation, 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - Graflex, Inc., 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - Hamilton Research Associates, Inc., 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - H R B - Singer, Inc., 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - Koncept-O-Graph Corporation, 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - Lectron Corporation of America, 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - New York Institute of Technology, 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - Philco-Philco Technological Center, 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - Programmed Teaching Aids, Inc., 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - Rheem Califone Corporation, 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - Science Research Associates, 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - Scientific Development Corporation, 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - TMC-Teaching Machines Corporation, 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - U. S. Industries, Inc., 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - Webster Electric, 1961 (Box II / 25)
      - Misc., 1961 (Box II / 25)
    - Teleprompter Corporation, 1959-1960 (Box II / 25)
    - Television Equipment, 1962 (Box II / 26)
    - Television Equipment, 1957 (Box II / 26)
    - Television Equipment, 1961 (Box II / 26)
    - U.S. Army (brochures), 1959 (Box II / 26)
    - University of Michigan (the), 1959 (Box II / 26)
    - Vega Electronics Corporation, 1961 (Box II / 26)
    - Video Tape Grant, 1960 (Box II / 26)